Hello welcome, it has been
recommended which is the auditor's results of the
quarter and date of March quarter
and the company's equity share at Rs 5.5 which
is 55% of the face value
% different company has recommended final
dividend and which will be approved in the Annual General Meeting,
so now we go to the
financial results of the company, so here
we have come to the financial results, the
numbers are given in the legs,
if we talk about income, then the income of the company
is Rs 5255 crore, in the last quarter the
income was Rs 4362 crore, in the March 22 quarter the
income was Rs 4600.36 crore, income order and
on and both are seeing a rise,
but here guys if you look at the company, if you
look at the expense in income, then the expense of the company is Rs
3978.78 crore, here the expense was Rs
4000.85 crore in the last March quarter
and in the March 22 quarter it was Rs 36
crore  There was an expense here, there was a
decline in the company's income, so the expense is also
declining quarter on quarter, but it is
visible in the expense because
gas is here, but in the income, but here the
income expense of the quadrant is declined, so
here the profit is expected to grow very fast,
if we
talk about the profit here, then if we look at the gas profit here, then the
net profit is Rs 436 crore, in the previous
quadrant it was Rs 30052 crore, on March 22, there was a
profit of Rs 30012 crore, quarter on
quarter, air on air, there is a rise in the profit of both,
if we talk about the app, then the app
which has come out here is Rs
8.9, in the last quadrant, since last year, there is a
very strong growth seen here, can you
see the gas and if we
look at the result of the company, the
company presented a very
good result this time,
now if we talk about
its segment avenue here, see, the company
generates revenue in many ways  Which includes
fire,
marine health including personal accident, out of which
health, retail health, group,
corporate health, government business, which
you can see here, there are many and
along with that the company does crop insurance,
motor, this premium efficiency, that is,
all these things
generated by the company are looking very good,
so now let us put the gas in the video, bye bye